

Email batool0604@gmail.com

Phone 923308112859

Location Pakistan Sindh Karachi

Address Sector 5-k, Apartment: Al-Hamra Avenue ft no: B-32, North Karchi. Karachi, Sindh

WORK EXPERIENCE

SM Public Academy Campus 2 | Pakistan Sindh Karachi

Computer teacher/ Lab instructor

Oct.2019 - Jul.2020

Worked well independently and on a team to solve problems.

Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.

Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner.

Fahim Abbasi's Students corner | Pakistan Sindh Karachi

Computer Lab instructor

Feb.2019 - Jul.2019

Served as a friendly, hardworking, and punctual employee.

Trueman school system | Pakistan Sindh Karachi

English language instructor

Sep.2018 - Dec.2018

Maintained an eagerness to add to my knowledge and skills.

EDUCATION

Dawood University of Engineering and Technology | Pakistan Sindh Karachi

Computer Science , BSCS

Dec.2018 - Present

St.Lawrence's govt degree girls college | Pakistan Sindh Karachi

Computer Science , Intermediate

Aug.2016 - Aug.2018

SM public Academy Campus 4 | Pakistan Sindh Karachi

Science , Matriculation

Mar.2004 - Mar.2016

SKILLS					
Microsoft Office					
Programming C,C++,Python,Rus	t				
Communication skills					
Content Writing/ Report Writing					

SUMMARY

Diligent university student who has never failed to meet a project deadline three years at DUET. Aiming to leverage my skills to land an internship for your company. Having ability to critical think and implement new ideas will help your company.

Also I have a huge interest in learning new technology and want to enhance my knowledge and skills.